<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>

	<string name="help_wallet">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			The upper left right of the screen displays your balance in Dash and one selected national currency.
			Tap to go to the list of national currencies, and tap on one of the currencies to select it as default.
		</p>
		<p>
			The QR code that contains your Dash address is accessed from the navigation menu (top left) and can be used for scanning by another party.
			Tap on the QR code to get a larger version of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			The bottom of the screen is covered by your transactions list, which is empty at the beginning.
			Pending transactions are greyed out until they are confirmed.
			Tap on one entry to see details or add the senders or receivers address to the address book.
			The address book is accessed from the navigation menu (top left).
		</p>
		<p>
			You can send or request coins by tapping the buttons in the action bar.
			More options are available in the navigation (top left) and options menus.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_request_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			Using this dialog, you can request coins from another person (who should already have installed Dash Wallet).
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you can enter an amount of Dash to request.
		</p>
		<p>
			Then, you either have the generated QR code scanned by the other person.
			Or, you can send your request to a remote person with the share button in the action bar.
			The other person will have to click the Dash URL.
		</p>
		<p>
			Either way, the other person will be presented a dialog for sending coins with all fields pre-populated.
			If she accepts, all she needs to do is send the payment.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_send_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			You have initiated the process of sending coins.
			You came here either through the main screen or by clicking on a Dash URL in your mobile browser.
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you enter the Dash address to pay to.
			The address will autocomplete from known entries in your address book.
			You can also scan QR codes with Dash addresses or Dash requests by pressing the QR button.
		</p>
		<p>
			Next, you can see how many Dash you can spend at the moment.
			Any difference to the balance from the main screen is still unconfirmed and can thus not yet be spent.
		</p>
		<p>
			Tap InstantSend if you intend to make an instant payment.  The fee is higher (0.01 DASH).
			Last, you enter the amount to pay.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can enter a payment while being offline.
			It will be sent on next restart of Dash Wallet.
			If you want a payment to be processed as fast as possible, make sure you are well connected (i.e. on a WLAN).
		</p>
		<p>
			Note:
			Payments are irreversible!
			Always check the receiving address.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>
	<string name="help_safety">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			<b>Important safety notes:</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			Dash are stored on the device.
			<b>If you lose it, you\'ll lose your Dash.</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			This means you need to <b>back up your wallet</b>!
			Use the in-app backup facility for this, rather than a third party backup app.
			Keep your backup safe and remember the password.
			This is an HD wallet.  Only one backup is required.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Before uninstalling</b> (or clearing app data/wiping your device), <b>transfer your Dash to another wallet</b>.
			Remaining Dash will be lost.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Payments are irreversible</b>.
			If you send your Dash into the void, there is almost no way to get them back.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Keep your mobile device safe!</b>
			Do not root your device.
			Do only install apps you fully trust.
			Malicious apps could be trying to steal your wallet.
		</p>
		<p>
			Keep the risk low!
			<b>Only use with small amounts</b> for day use.
		</p>
	]]>
	</string>

</resources>
